麦克斯 我去个厕所 你帮我盯一下
Max, can you watch my tables while I run to the restroom?
早就在盯了
I already am.
我盯着那个假装
I've been watching model girl
吃东西的小模特30分钟了
pretend she's eating for 30 minutes.
她人很好呢
Oh, she's nice.
不管吃不吃 该给小费不会少
She always tips on what she would've eaten.
大家快来猜猜看
Guess what, everyone?
我有一个小秘密
I have a secret.
你是女儿心 男儿身吗
You're a woman trapped in a man's body?
不是
No.
你是男儿心 女儿身吗
You're a man trapped in a woman's body?
你是男童心 女童身吗
You're a little boy trapped in a little girl's body?
我是男儿心 在男儿身里
I am a man in a man's body.
我们对你在男人身里还是身下没兴趣
We're not talking about your night life.
我在翻查员工简历时
I have discovered something
发现了件事
when going over the employee applications.
好吧 其实我没在
Okay, perhaps I never worked at
华道夫·阿斯多里亚酒店工作过
the Waldorf Astoria,
但我的确跟华道夫 在阿斯多里亚市工作过
but I did work with this guy, Waldorf, in Astoria.
跟你无关
It's not you.
明天是卡洛琳的生日
Tomorrow is Caroline's birthday.
为什么我会不知道
Why wouldn't I know that?
她什么鸡毛蒜皮的破事都告诉我
She tells me everything about her life.
我就是太了解她的生理周期
I know so much about her cycle,
以至于不搞大她肚子 我感觉好罪过
I'm feeling pressure to impregnate her.
我可以代劳哟
I can do that for you.
太奇怪了
It's weird.
她怎么会不想庆祝生日呢
Why wouldn't she want to celebrate her birthday?
她什么屁事都要庆祝一下
She celebrates everything.
给大伙通报一下
Heads up, everybody.
我刚把厕纸补上了哦
I just refilled the paper towels.
谁最有团队精神 是我 是我
Who's a team player? What, what?
麦克斯
Max.
你懂我们该干什么吧
You know what we have to do.
靠 我就知道会有这么一天
Aw, man. I knew this day would come.
好吧 我最少得"牺牲"多少才能保住饭碗
All right, what's the least amount I can do to keep my job?
搞完了 记得告诉我
Just tell me when it's over.
开始前 记得打个招呼
And when it starts.
我是来跟你讨论卡洛琳的生日
It's time to talk about Caroline's birthday.
你得给她办个派对啊
You have to throw her a party.
还不如让你这只"小鸟"办了得了
I'd rather you just have your tiny way with me.
我讨厌生日 我连自己的生日都不知道
I don't like birthdays. I don't even know when mine is.
我妈最多也就把范围缩小到六月的某两周
My mom narrowed it down to a two-week window in June.
可你是卡洛琳的超级死党啊
But you are Caroline's BFF.
超级死党就要帮朋友办生日派对
And it is BFF's job to throw friend a party.
阿憨 我不够钱帮她搞派对
Han, I don't have enough money to throw a party.
我甚至连搞个棒球玩的钱都没有
I don't even have enough money to throw a baseball.
你有钱 你当她的超级死党啊
You have money. You be her BFF.
我已经有超级死党了 他叫杰马克斯
I already have a BFF-- Jamarcus.
我上次生日
And my last birthday,
他帮我办了个超屌的派对
he threw me a sick surprise party.
超级死党可不是死要面子的意思
You must think BFF stands for "Barely Freaking Friends",
你哪可能跟叫"杰马克斯"
because there's no way you're down
这帅气名字的人当上朋友啊
with someone named Jamarcus.
你确定咩
Oh, really?
不是死党 怎么会告诉对方银行卡密码啊
Then why did we exchange ATM pin numbers?
我把那里去掉 一切就搞定了
I'll just crop that, and we'll be good to go.
麦克斯 艾德温把我们的网站设计好了
Max, Edwin's ready to show us the design for our new website.
快来看看
Come see it.
兄台 你天天跟网站大师谈"公事"
Dude, you and the webmaster have been talking "business"
谈了整整一周
every day for a week.
是不是有猫腻啊
Is something going on there?
网站也早该"大湿"了吧
Shouldn't the web be mastered by now?
我们是纯公事
It's strictly business.
随便吧 不过既然花了200块
All right, but it's costing us $200.
"捞点油水"回来也不错啊
Might as well get something out of it.
要不让他"上上"你的"呀呼"
Maybe let him browse your Yahoo?
他貌似有个超多"内存"的
Looks like he might have a big ol' hard drive
生猛"大硬"盘哦
with a lot of ram.
他是不错
Yeah, he's cute,
可我现在不想谈恋爱
but I don't want a relationship right now.
我也不搞一夜情[一夜站]
And I don't do one-night stands.
那好 别站着 躺下搞好了
All right, so don't stand. Lay down.
我不喜欢
That's not me--
隔天早上 步履沉重 满脸羞愧地离开
the next morning, doing the walk of shame.
我鄙视那些顶着一夜激情后的乱发
I always see those girls with their messed-up sex hair,
一手提高跟鞋 一手拉紧大衣
carrying their heels, clutching their coats
盖住身上前晚的衣服
to hide last night's outfit.
走进金考印刷店 用谷歌地图
Going into Kinko's to use Google maps
定位自己身在何处的女人
so you can figure out where you are.
金考都让你用成"精拷"了
You really put the "ho" In "Kinko."
抱歉 苏菲
Oh. Sorry, Sophie.
我们关门了
We're closed.
别啊 我很快的
Oh, no. I'll be quick.
我打包个小蛋糕就走
I just want a cupcake to go.
我要去24小时健身房了
I'm on my way to 24 hour fitness.
我要把小蛋糕放跑步机上激励自己
Ya, and I put it on the cupcake holder on the treadmill.
麦克斯 我的加长轿车就停在外面
Uh, Max, my town car is parked out front
要不要我等你们一下
and I was wondering if you wanted me to wait
让你们搭我顺风车回家
for you and Caroline to give you a ride back to our building.
不用了 没关系
Oh, no. It's okay.
我们还得留下打扫 把垃圾拿去丢掉呢
We still have to clean up and take the garbage out.
貌似垃圾把自己丢出来了
Oh, looks like the garbage is taking itself out.
爱情游戏继续
The game continues.
这是我的电话
Here is my number.
诚挚邀请你来电
I invite you to call me
想通要谈 拨打热线 立刻上门
when you realize what a catch I am.
喝醉约炮 一通电话 使命必达
Or any time you are drunk and willing.
麦克斯 我还想要个小垃圾袋
Max, I'm going to need the doggy bag as well.
不是要装蛋糕
Not for the cupcake.
是要吐
To puke in.
我会把一切搞定
So I'll get this finalized,
明天再来一趟餐厅
and then I'll stop by the diner tomorrow
等你验收完效果 网站就能上线啦
so you can sign off on the layout before we go live.
好兴奋好期待啊
This is so exciting.
擦 等等 艾德温
Oh, wait, Edwin. Shoot.
我差点忘了给你新的价目表
I forgot to show you the new pricing chart.
没事 我可以立马处理
It's cool, I can draft it up right now
然后回家就把这上传了
and upload it when I get home.
网站大师 你挺"快"的嘛
Yeah, webmaster. You work pretty fast.
我猜你也懂得怎么"慢慢搞"...
But I bet you can work slow, too.
然后再"快快搞"的吧
And really fast again.
我一分钟就能搞完
I can be done in a minute.
啊哦 最不想听到的话
Ooh, not what you want to hear.
麦克斯
Max.
不用急 我们可以等
It's fine. We can wait.
这样吧 你在这等
You know what? You stay here.
我得去买点东西 给你的...
I have to go to the store and pick up stuff for your--
我的什么
my what?
你硬拉我入伙的小蛋糕生意
Your cupcake business that you're making me do with you.
路上小心
Get home safe.
你住哪里呢 艾德温
Um, hey, where do you live, Edwin?
地狱厨房[曼哈顿的一个区]
Hell's kitchen.
挺好
Oh, cool.
到时候你就坐C号线
You're going to want to take the "C" down,
转L号线就行了 如果迷路
transfer to the "L," and if you get lost,
6街与14街交叉口有间金考印刷店
there's a Kinko's on 6th and 14th.
真不好意思 麦克斯只是...
That's embarrassing. Max was just trying to--
复杂的网站编程都难不倒我
Yeah, I work on complicated web programs.
破解她的潜台词易如反掌
I think I cracked that code.
她想撮合咱俩嘛
She wants us to hook up.
是啊 真抱歉
Yeah. I'm sorry.
干嘛抱歉
Why are you sorry?
这也是我日思夜想的事
That's all I've been thinking about.
美味 真美味
Yum, yum.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
天雷勾动地火啊
They are so hot.
少这么看我
Don't give me that look.
奥列格
Oleg.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
你又怎么会在这儿
我住这里
I live here,
我刚出去买杯咖啡
and I'm just coming out from going to get coffee.
太好喝了 我一滴都没剩下
It was delicious. I drank every bit of it.
在外面就喝光了 所以现在手里没咖啡
Outside. That's why I don't have a cup.
可你还穿着昨晚的衣服呢
But you're wearing the same outfit from last night.
你也穿着昨晚的衣服啊
You're wearing the same outfit from last night.
你顶着一头激情过后的乱发
And you have messed-up sex hair.
你也顶着一头激情过后的乱发
You have messed-up sex hair.
网站大师吗
Webmaster?
苏菲吗
Sophie?
她打给我 我们"手交"了
She called me up and we made hand love.
苏菲不是很讨厌你吗
But I thought Sophie hated you.
她又不讨厌我的手
Well, she doesn't hate my hand.
你不可以告诉别人哦
But you cannot tell anyone.
那是她的条件之一
That was her one condition.
还有就是由合格医生签名的
That and a copy of my recent blood tests
近期验血报告
signed by a medical professional.
没问题
Deal.
你也不许跟别人透半句口风
And you can't tell anyone about me, either.
尤其不能让麦克斯知道
Especially Max.
她会没完没了的
I'd never hear the end of it.
没问题
Deal.
拉钩约定吗
Pinky swear?
算了 还是别了
Actually, never mind.
我不知道你的脏手还摸过什么
I don't know where your fingers have been.
我不是才告诉你它们摸过什么吗
I just told you where they've been.
麦克斯
Max
我好期待这个派对啊
I'm so excited for this party.
我穿了宽松衣服来 以便彻夜热舞
I wore my loose clothing so I can dance all night.
天啊 派对的压力快让我崩溃了
God, I cannot take this party pressure.
我要去后面
I'm just going to go in the back
用开罐器割腕自尽了
and run a can opener across my wrist.
麦克斯 你肯定行的
Oh, Max. I'm sure you did a great job.
只要有DJ
You know, as long as you have a DJ,
有香槟 外加个灵媒就行
some champagne, and a psychic.
没DJ 没香槟 没灵媒
No, no, and no.
只有气球 鹰嘴豆泥
I got some balloons, a hummus tray,
还有不一定来的厄尔
and possibly Earl.
他没给我准信
He still hasn't confirmed.
不用灵媒 也知道
You don't need psychic to know
这肯定会是个坏坏的派对了
that this is going to be a horrible, horrible party.
幸好卡洛琳有了新的小男仆
Well, thank God Caroline has new boy toy.
她应该不会太介意
She might not mind as much.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我昨晚看到他们在餐厅外面接吻了
Yeah, I saw them kissing in front of the diner last night.
没错 我坐在那里看了整整一小时呢
Yeah, I sat there and watched for an hour.
他们天雷勾动地火 一发不可收拾
They were really going at it, hot and heavy.
尺度就跟昔日美好的重口电视台一样
You know, like the Showtime network in the good old days.
这下可好
Oh, great.
还得多请个人来参加派对
Now I have to invite him to the party, too?
我只准备了六包可沛利果汁呢
I only got a six-pack of Capri Suns,
现在得排排坐 分果汁了
so people are going to have to share.
恭喜我们 我们的网站
Congratulations, it's official.
正式上线了
Our website is now live.
恭喜 我们的卡洛琳
Congratulations, it's official.
正式浪荡了
You're a whore.
听说你到金考印刷店"报到"了
I hear you got your Kinko's card punched.
什么
What?
少跟我装蒜
Don't "what" me.
我知道你跟网站大师搞上了
I know you hooked up with the webmaster.
上菜
Pick up.
奥列格 是你告诉麦克斯的吗
Oleg, you told Max?
什么情况
What's happening?
你做初一 我做十五
Our deal's off.
奥列格跟苏菲昨晚上床了
Oleg had sex with Sophie last night.
没有啊
No...
我们没上床 只是"上手"而已
It wasn't sex. Just hand stuff.
腰部以上也没让他侵犯
Yeah, and nothing above the waist.
我可是位淑女
I'm a lady.
人家看卡洛琳跟"大憨"激情四射后忍不住嘛
I got all hot and bothered watching Caroline and big Han.
好吧...
Okay...
这是我跟卡洛琳之间的私事吧
You know, I really think this is between Caroline and me.
你是说你跟卡洛琳 还有你的脱衣舞女吧
You mean between Caroline, you, and your strippers.
什么脱衣舞女
Strippers?
我在脱衣舞厅里见过这男的
I have seen this man in a strip club.
阿憨 你还去过脱衣舞厅啊
Han, you were in a strip club?
厄尔带我去的
Earl took me.
我靠 阿憨
Damn it, Han.
我没抖出你
You're going to sell me out
装大款的事 你还敢出卖我
after I spotted you $100 in ones.
你们居然撇下我去"开腿见喜"
You went to Spreaders without me?
你怎么会带阿憨去脱衣舞厅啊
Why would you take Han to a strip club?
他的小短腿能让人坐上去跳艳舞吗
Yeah, is his lap even big enough for a dance?
厄尔 我对你太失望了
Earl, I'm so disappointed in you.
够了 老子不参加你的派对了
That's it. I'm not going to your party.
什么派对
What party?
我靠 厄尔
Damn it, Earl!
这可是生日惊喜派对啊
It's supposed to be a surprise for her birthday.
谁告诉你我生日的
Who told you it was my birthday?
阿憨
Han.
我靠 阿憨
Damn it, Han!
我不想要生日派对
I didn't want a party
我今年不想庆祝生日
and I don't want to celebrate my birthday this year.
那惨了
Well, too bad,
你的超级死党为你准备了个超级派对
because your BFF is throwing you a big blow-out.
麦克斯 我对不起你
Oh, Max. Now I feel bad.
别急 派对开始 就知道是谁对不起谁了
You feel bad now, wait till you see the party.
卡洛琳过生日啦 呜呼 呜呼
Caroline's birthday. Woot, woot.
谢谢 这些话不说也没差啦
Thanks, but you don't have to say that after everything.
麦克斯
Max...
我知道你预算不高
I know you had limited budget,
但是音乐是免费的呀
but music is free.
是啊 可是老娘就是不爽放
Yeah, well, I'm a douche.
致辞
Speech!
这派对我独木难支啊
I can't carry this party much longer.
好吧 我来说几句话
Okay, I'd like to say something.
等等
Wait, wait.
不能等切蛋糕完再致辞吗
Can't we wait till we cut the cake?
蛋糕
Cake?
这年头大家还吃蛋糕啊
People are still doing that?
是啊 我们不就是卖蛋糕维生的吗
Yes. Our livelihood depends on it.
世界上比这个还糟的派对只有一个
There's only one party as bad as this one.
唐纳派对[组织]
That's the Donner Party.
人家吃的都比咱们好
And even they had better food.
我想祝这位美若天仙的姑娘生日快乐
I'd like to say happy birthday to a very pretty lady
与她相遇真是三生有幸
who I just had the pleasure of meeting,
希望未来能对她有更深入的了解
and I think I'm going to be seeing a lot more of her.
我去帮咱们再拿点饮料
I'll go get us some more drinks.
好的
Okay.
帮我甩掉他
Get rid of him.
什么
What?
我跟他只是一夜情
It was a one-time thing.
你不是不搞一夜情的人吗
I thought you weren't that kind of girl.
我突然想起我有将近一年
I realized it had almost been a year
没有被男人"滋润"过了
since I had sex,
一夜风流总比饥渴难耐好吧
and I decided I rather not be that kind of girl.
可我不想跟他谈恋爱
But I don't want a relationship.
我懂 "打"完就跑
Hey, I get it. Hit it and quit it.
* 打完了 就别留着了 *
* Hit it, don't babysit it *
麦克斯 别闹了
Max, please.
好啦
Fine.
我怎么才能把他弄走啊
How am I going to make him go away?
这派对烂成这样
It's not going to take a lot
劝人离开有难度吗
to convince someone to leave this party.
我很想请大家都举起鸡尾酒
I'd like to ask everyone to raise their cocktail,
可惜无法实现
but I can't.
只好请大家向日举起果汁
So raise your Capri to the sun...
敬一位与众不同的女士
For a very special lady
我相信我会对她有更深入的了解
who I'm sure I will be seeing more of.
帮我甩掉他 我跟他只是一夜情
Get rid of him. It was a one-time thing.
这是你去过最烂的派对吗
So was that the worst party you've ever been to?
是个人都会这么觉得吧
That was the worst party anyone's ever been to.
跟网站大师搞上 那方面如何
So with the webmaster, how was the sex?
不错啊
Pretty good.
直到他跟我玩窒息式性爱
But then he did that thing where he pretended
假装想掐死我
he was going to choke me.
男人什么时候开始玩这招了啊
When did guys start doing that?
我不知道
I don't know,
早知道他会这么玩
but if I knew that was his thing,
我真该叫他在派对上掐死我
I would've asked him to choke me at the party.
你怎么帮我甩掉他的
How did you get rid of him?
你跟人家说了什么 有好好跟人说吗
What did you say? Did you let him down gently?
没 我让他有多远滚多远
No, I told him to hit the pike.
反正就是一夜情嘛 男人懂的
It's a one-night stand. Guys get that.
就这样吗 他没伤心吗
So that's it? He wasn't upset?
男人才不在乎
Guys don't care.
一夜情嘛 来完[高潮] 就走了
One-night stands-- they come, they go.
就是这么一回事
Literally.
要是他以后想再续前缘怎么办
But what if he wants to see me again?
别紧张啦
Relax.
他才不会回来对你死缠烂打
It is not going to come back to haunt you.
除非你感到生理有需要
Unless you start feeling an itch...
或肚里有动静
Or a kick.
谢谢你帮我甩了他
Well, thanks for dumping him.
也谢谢你那...
And for the...
那个所谓的"派对"吧
I'm going to go ahead and call it a party.
我知道你不会想我用咱们的开店基金
I knew you wouldn't want me to use any of the cupcake money,
我自己又没钱
and I was broke.
所以我现在算是你的超级死党了吧
So I guess I am your BFF--
超级死穷鬼党
your broke friend forever.
麦克斯 其实什么派对都没有用
Max, it really doesn't matter what you would've done.
我唯一想要的生日礼物
The only thing I really wanted for my birthday
是见我老爸一面
was to see my father.
而他又在牢里 所以没戏
And he's in prison, so that didn't happen.
或许我不是个好死党
I may not be a good BFF,
或许我不懂怎么办好派对
I may not throw a great party,
可我知道去哪里坐免费监狱巴士
but I do know where to find a free bus to prison.
大家好 车上有个小寿星哦
Hey, everybody. We got a birthday girl onboard.
屁股给我乖乖粘回椅子上
Sit yo ass back down!
看吧 有个真的派对啦
See? Now we got a party.
离开市中心感觉挺不错啊
This is nice getting out of the city.
让我想起去汉普顿度假的情景
Kind of reminds me of the ride to the Hamptons.
喂
Yo.
你们第一次上开搞巴士吗
This your first time on the bangbus?
之所以叫这名字
We call it the bangbus
是因为乘客都是去牢里跟伴侣开搞的
because everybody here gonna get banged.
而且这是巴士嘛 所以叫"开搞巴士"
And in addition 'cause we're on a bus.
言之有理
Hmm, makes sense.
我叫珊妲
Hey, I'm Shonda.
我叫麦克斯 她叫卡洛琳
I'm Max. This is Caroline.
你们都是要去"探亲"的吗
So you're all going for, like, conjugal visits?
这说法还真是文绉绉啊
Pretty fancy term for getting
不就是去"救赎"一下饥渴的肖申克嘛
shawshanked on a three-legged cot.
肖申克的"救赎" 我喜欢你这词
Shawshanked. I like her.
我也喜欢你的发型
I like your hair.
刚从墨西哥度假回来吗
Did you just get back from Cancun?
不是不是
No, no.
这我特地为我男人弄得
I saved up, and I got these done for my man.
他说这发型让我看起来像艾莉西亚·凯斯
He says they make me look like Alicia Keys
加在美国X历史中的爱德华·诺顿
meets Ed Norton in American History X.
真甜蜜
How sweet.
你男人又因何入狱的呢
Ah, yo. What's your man in for?
我男人是因为非法持有一对完美小翘臀
My man's in for possession of a sweet, sweet ass.
他每次都得说这个烂笑话
He makes that joke every time.
其实我不是去看男人 是去看我爸
He's not my man, actually. He's my dad.
原来你是变态啊
Oh, so you're a freak.
没事的 我才不会乱批判别人
That's all right. I don't judge.
我身上又没有名牌写着"法官朱迪"[美国节目]
You see a name tag on me that says "Judy"?
快看 我们刚路过一家凯菲
Oh, look. We just passed a Carvel.
什么是凯菲啊
What's a Carvel?
凯菲冰激凌啊
Carvel ice cream.
他们的软糖鲸鱼 饼干猫没听过吗
You know, Fudgie the Whale, Cookie Puss.
不是吧 怎么可能没听过凯菲冰激凌
Come on, how could you not know Carvel?
他们的冰激凌车随处可见
They have them everywhere.
等等
Oh, wait.
就是穷苦白人吃的冰激凌吗
Is that that white trash ice cream?
你再说一次试试
How dare you!
才不是穷苦白人吃的
It is not white trash.
而且你也别装什么高贵了
And I wouldn't be so high and mighty.
你正坐在通往监狱的免费巴士上呢
You're on a free bangbus to a prison.
真是抱歉哦
I'm sorry.
我没想到你对冰激凌
I didn't realize you had such
有如此强烈的感情
a strong emotional connection to ice cream.
不是冰激凌 是冰激凌蛋糕
Not to the ice cream. The ice cream cake.
我十岁时 我让我妈给我办生日派对
When I was ten, I asked my mom for a birthday party.
她答应之后 又睡过去了
She said yes but then flaked out
没邀请任何人来
and forgot to call anyone.
现在我懂为什么
I'm starting to understand why
你不喜欢生日派对了
you don't like birthday parties.
我在阳台干等了一个小时后
So after I waited on the porch for an hour,
就去她皮包偷了20块
I'll stole 20 bucks from her purse,
拦了一辆冰激凌车
thumbed it out to Carvel,
然后买了软糖鲸鱼冰激凌蛋糕吃
and bought myself a Fudgie the Whale cake.
用一根小粉勺把它全部吃光
Ate the whole thing with a pink plastic spoon,
那种幸福感 是任何生日派对都比不上的
and it was way better than any party ever could have been.
我全听见了
I heard that.
软糖鲸鱼冰激凌蛋糕最棒了
There ain't nothing better than Fudgie the Whale.
我最爱巧克力碎果仁口味
I love the chocolate crunchies.
白痴 谁不爱那个口味啊
Bitch, everybody love the damn chocolate crunchies!
珊妲 你是来探视谁呢
Hey, Shonda. Who are you here to see?
谁有空啊
Who's available?
开玩笑嘛 我当然是来找蠕爷的
I'm just cracking wise. You know I'm here to see Squirm.
搜查她全身吧
Search her.
靠 怎么又是我
Damn. Is it my turn again?
下一位
Next.
我们没在名单上 我们没预约
We're not on that list. We didn't call ahead.
我来处理
Leave it to me.
我没有想进却进不去的地方
I've gotten into every club I've ever wanted to get into.
卡洛琳·钱宁 带一朋友
Hi. Caroline Channing plus one.
你不在名单上啊
I don't see you on the list.
真的吗 怪事
Really? That's weird.
我们应该在名单上啊 一直都是这样
We should be on the list. We're always on the list.
麦克斯 我们不在名单上
Max, we're not on the list.
不在名单上吗 我要宰了我助理
We're not? I'm going to kill my assistant.
我知道了
Oh, I know.
应该是在德安杰洛·杰佛逊的名下吧
It might be under Deangelo Jefferson.
女士们 别浪费我时间了
Come on, girls. Don't waste my time.
我要见你们主管
I'd like to see a manager.
这里没有主管
There's no manager.
这里是监狱
It's a prison.
那这里谁管事
Well, then who runs this place?
雅利安兄弟会最近势力挺庞大的
Well, the Aryan brotherhood is getting pretty strong.
真是石头脑袋不开窍
This is such amateur hour.
给我50块塞给这看门的吧
Give me 50 bucks for the door guy.
你不会是真想在
Are you seriously trying to bribe
监狱里贿赂一名警官吧
an officer of the law while inside a prison?
这可是重罪
That's a federal offense.
真的吗
Is it?
应该吧
Probably.
光冲着你们这想法 我就该把你们轰出去
Look, I should have you thrown out for even suggesting it.
我们这里不收贿赂
We do not accept bribes.
好吧 好吧
Okay, fine.
如果你放我们进去 做全身检查时
I'll let you take your sweet time searching me
我让你检查"到底"呢
on the way in.
这两位女士可以进去了
These two are clear to go through.
麦克斯 你不需要为我这么牺牲
Max, you can't do that for me.
我是为了自己 好久没人"碰"过我了
It's really for me. It's been a while.
哟呵 哟呵
Woot, woot.
等了这么久
I'm so excited to see my father
终于能见我爸了
after all this time.
我看起来如何
How do I look?
你看起来挺好 我呢
You look good. How do I look?
还有着刚被人"检查"完的光彩吗
Do I still have that freshly felt-up glow?
那边的红发男对你挺有兴趣呢
Well, that ginger over there thinks you look good.
他目不转睛地盯着你呢
He's full-on staring at you.
没人看才惨呢
Well, I should hope so.
在母猪都能赛貂蝉的监狱里都没人看
If you can't get a dude in prison to check you out,
你就该去野猪大改造了
it's time for a makeover.
不是 他是边打量边点头
No, he's looking and nodding
好像认识你似的
like he knows you.
素未蒙面 绝对不认识
Never seen him before in my life.
麦克斯
Max?
麦克斯·布莱克
Max Black?
是我啊 爱尔兰男啊
It's me, Irish.
你说啥呢 兄弟 认错人了吧
I don't know, dude. I think you got the wrong girl.
麦克斯 我永远不会忘记你的样子
Max, I could never forget that face.
相信我 我们绝对素未蒙面
Trust me, you've never seen me before.
哇靠
Oh, damn!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
是你耶
That's you.
现在记得了吧
So you do remember.
当然记得
Of course.
帮我甩掉他 我跟他只是一夜情
Get rid of him. It was a one-night stand.
看吧 果真是会回来死缠烂打的
See, they do come back to haunt you.
衣服穿好
Shirt on.
麦克斯 你敢相信吗
Max, can you believe it?
世界上有那么多监狱
Of all the prisons in all the world,
你却走进我这家
you walked into mine.
这就是命运
It's kismet.
我帮过你 现在轮到你帮我了
I got rid of yours. You get rid of mine.
听我说 爱尔兰男 当年只是一夜春宵
Listen, Irish. It was a one-time thing.
你是男人 你懂得吧
You're a guy. You get that.
可一夜夫妻白日恩啊
How could you say it's a one-time thing?
我爱你
I love you.
我为你炸了那间墨西哥餐馆呢
I blew up that chipotle for you.
我很感谢你为我纹身
Listen, I appreciate the ink,
但我不相信爱情
but I don't really believe in love,
而且老实说
and truth be told,
我根本不爱墨西哥菜
I'm not even a fan of Mexican food.
卡洛琳·钱宁 这桌
Caroline Channing. This table.
麦克斯 我们坐过去吧 我老爸要来了
Max, we have to go. My dad's coming.
好了 很高兴与你重逢 爱尔兰男
Okay. Nice to see you, Irish.
你的身材看起来酷毙了
Your body looks sick.
麦克斯 等等
Max, hold on.
这是最后一次警告
I'm not going to tell you again to back up.
麦克斯 我不想再次失去你
Max, I'm not going to lose you twice.
我说了 退后
I said, back up!
别叫我退后
Don't tell me to back up.
她是我一生的挚爱
That's the love of my life.
兄弟 有多远滚多远吧
Come on, dude. Hit the pike.
冷静下来
Calm down.
别叫我冷静
Don't tell me to calm down!
会面时间结束 所有人出去
Visiting hours are over! Everybody out!
不不不 不行 我不能走
No, no, no, wait! I can't leave.
靠
Damn!
等等 那是我老爸
Oh, wait. There's my father.
我看到他的身影了 他要出来了
I can see him, he's just coming in.
老爸 老爸 看到我了吗
Oh, daddy. Daddy... Hi!
感谢你们俩全家啊 小姐们
Well, thank you very much, ladies.
我男人才刚"进入" 我就被"拉出"了
My man was barely in when I got pulled out.
我想给大家道个歉
I would like to apologize to everyone
害开搞巴士的各位开搞失败
for taking the bang out of the bus,
我想为自己解释
but in my own defense,
在座各位也都懂疯子疯起来的样子嘛
everyone here knows a little something about crazy guys.
屁股给我乖乖粘回椅子上
Sit yo ass back down!
麦克斯赶紧坐下吧 不然等会又暴动了
Max, sit down before you start another riot.
对不起 我搞砸了一切
I'm sorry. I blew it.
我搞砸了你见你老爸的机会
I screwed up your chance to see your father.
我办砸了你的派对
I screwed up your party.
我连庆祝生日最简单的方式
I even screwed up the easiest birthday thing to do,
买个蛋糕都不会
like get a cake.
我真是个超烂死党
I'm a terrible BFF.
没关系的
It's okay.
真的没关系
Really, it's fine.
今年我经历的一切
With the year I'm having,
也不是你随便买个蛋糕
it's not like you could've made everything better
就能好转起来的
just by getting me a cake.
的确 普通的蛋糕不行
Well, no. Not just any cake.
跟我记忆中的一样美味
Just as good as I remember it.
我们花得最值的40块
Best 40 bucks we ever spent.
这个生日其实也不错嘛
And this birthday turned out to be all right.
我的愿望有实现
I did get what I wanted.
我见到了我老爸
I got see my father.
虽然只有短暂的一秒 但的确是见到了
It was only for a second, but I saw him.
他也看见我了 所以谢谢你
And he saw me. So thank you.
是啊 我也跟爱尔兰男重逢了
Yeah, and I got to see Irish.
或许跟他是情深缘浅
Think he might be the one that got away.
警察还对他抓住不放呢
Well, the one that got put away.
我跟你可不只是超级死党哦
You know, you and I are better than BFFs.
我们是搞巴死党
We're BBFs.
开搞巴士死党
Bangbus friends.